<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Sports &#8211; Staging Reliability Uptake</title>
	<atom:link href="/category/sports/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 09:36:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/live-favicon.jpg</url>
	<title>Sports &#8211; Staging Reliability Uptake</title>
	<link></link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Nigeria Stuns Australia Portugal Gets First Win</title>
		<link>/nigeria-stuns-australia-portugal-gets-first-win/</link>
					<comments>/nigeria-stuns-australia-portugal-gets-first-win/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 15:29:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nigeria Stuns Australia Portugal Gets First Win]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=50</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[All week, Australian soccer officials have urged the country’s news media and its army of fans to focus on the players healthy enough to take the field for the team representing the tournament co-hosts. Those efforts have been largely futile, with the fate of star striker Sam Kerr and her injured right calf being the...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify;">All week, Australian soccer officials have urged the country’s news media and its army of fans to focus on the players healthy enough to take the field for the team representing the tournament co-hosts. Those efforts have been largely futile, with the fate of star striker Sam Kerr and her injured right calf being the dominant narrative of the country’s World Cup so far.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">A victory over Nigeria would have guaranteed a spot in the round of 16, and would have perhaps given some respite and the chance to rest what has become the most talked about calf muscle in Australia for at least one more game. But a shock defeat to Nigeria, which scored three times after Australia struck first in front of more than 40,000 fans in Brisbane, leaves Australia’s hopes of making it to the knockout stage dangling precariously and the need for a rescue act from Kerr more urgent than ever.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">Australia now faces a shootout against Canada, the champion of the Tokyo Olympics, on Monday with anything but a victory likely to lead to an untimely and embarrassing exit for a team that had high hopes of going deep in the tournament. For Nigeria, the path forward is clearer an much more favorable: A tie with already eliminated Ireland guarantees progress. After requiring a second half penalty to overcome Ireland in a scrappy tournament opener, Australia’s players talked the pressure of being tournament hosts, with the hopes of a country on their shoulders. Against Nigeria, that same anxiety was clearly present.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Passes were fluffed, chances were snatched and arms were thrown in the air in frustration.</strong></p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">With the first half almost up, that fog of uncertainty looked like it had cleared as Australia put together a collection of passes to thread its way through Nigeria. Emily van Egmond, a replacement for another injured Australian striker, Mary Fowler, met the ball and scored with a perfectly timed run. Van Egmond instantly turned toward the touchline and into the waiting arms of Kerr, whose embrace showed relief as much as joy.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">But Australia’s hopes of a peaceful night evaporated almost as soon as the celebrations had died down. Nigeria launched a last attack before halftime, and thanks to a fortunate deflection, the ball found its way to Uchenna Kanu, whose deft finish instantly sucked the joy out of the Australian crowd. A moment of silence hit in the stadium, punctuated by yelps from flecks in the stands where heavily outnumbered Nigerian supporters had gathered.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">Nigeria, newly emboldened, scored twice more in the second half as Australia’s anxiety mounted, its scrambled thinking creating the type of openings that Nigeria could not pass up. Poor defending from a corner from Australia allowed the ball to eventually find its way to defender Osinachi Ohale to score at the far post. A substitute, Asisat Oshoala, then took advantage of a mix-up between defender Alanna Kennedy and goalkeeper Mackenzie Arnold to give Nigeria a two-goal lead that led to delirious celebrations on the Nigerian bench.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">Kennedy scored with a header in injury time, but by then the damage had been done, and Australia’s fate, for one night at least, was sealed. While Nigeria’s players danced in celebration after what is certainly its most eye-catching success at a World Cup, the vanquished hosts huddled, the entire roster taking part in an on-field demonstration of togetherness at a time of crisis.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Yet it will be one name that will now, more than ever, be invoked. The calls for Kerr will reach a fever pitch.</strong></p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">Australia Coach Tony Gustavsson, still reeling from his team’s shocked defeat, acknowledged that Kerr’s health would dominate the days leading to what is now a critical game. “It might even be where we need to test her on game day — that’s how tight it is,” Gustavsson said. He added that he knew Kerr, the team’s leader, would “do anything to be out there.”</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/nigeria-stuns-australia-portugal-gets-first-win/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
